OK. I need to speak to my boyfriend
in private, like, right now.
(Howard:)There's a car with a glass roof.
Want to go look at the stars?
(Bernadette:)-That sounds so romantic.
-Give it a rest!
(Penny:)Let's go.
(Amy:)-Why are you still here?
-Excuse me.
(Sheldon:)I think you're being a little rude.
(Amy:)I'm being rude? You've been
rude to me this entire evening.
(Sheldon:)How is that possible?
(Sheldon:)I've hardly spoken
to you since we got on the train.
(Man:)I'm detecting a little
friction between you two,
(Man:)and I don't want to be a third rail.
(Man:)Get it?
(Sheldon:)I get it.
Leave!
(Sheldon:)-What is your problem?
-it's Valentine's Day.
(Amy:)We're supposed to be
having a romantic weekend.
(Sheldon:)Oh, really?
Because I remember you saying
(Sheldon:)that this trip was going to be
something we could both enjoy.
(Sheldon:)Did you mean that,
or were you just trying to trick me?